













Baranova Natalia Frontend Developer

I'm a result oriented energetic front-end developer with experience in building web interfaces. Every day I work on my skills in this direction and expanding them with new knowledge. Currently I'm learning React Native. My plans is to learn ExpressJS. I solve katas on codewars.com. I value my own time very hight, that's why it's better for me to have a remote work. But I can consider an office job too, depends on opportunities that it could provide me with.

Contact Me

- □ baranova.natalia.frontend@gmail.com
- +54 9 11-6158-1255 (WhatsApp/Telegram)
- Moscow, Russia
- portfolio site

Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript
- JS libraries and frameworks: ReactJS, React Native,
- State management libraries: Redux(toolkit), Thunk, RTK-query
- Routing: React-router-DOM, React Navigation
- Forms: React-formik, React-form, React-hookform
- Testing: Unit, Jest, Snapshot image test, Postman
- Patterns: TDD, Singleton, Observer, PubSub
- API: Axios, Rest, Swagger
- Storybook
- Version control: GitHub, GitLab
- Styles: CSS, Sass, Scss, styled components
- Design libraries: Material UI, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap

Work Experience

Friendlee.pro - frontend dev

2024-2024

Web-studio. NextJS, Zustand, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript Федеральная сеть центров по диагностике и лечению <u>онкозаболеваний</u>

Конкурс мобильной фотографии

2021-2022 Lemma-auto - fullstack developer It's a shop of autoparts. Laravel 8, php, MySQL, html, sass, native JavaScript, bootstrap, tailwind

2020-2021 Mos.ru - backend developer The main portal of the city of Moscow. Symfony5

• Labirint.ru - fullstack developer 2020-2020 This is a bookstore. Yii2, native JS, html, css

Ministry of Economic Development -2011-2020 database developer MS Access Development of an internal database for regulatory documents in MS Access.

My responsibilities:

work in a command, meet ups developing user interface, implementing pagination, search and sort of data, working with Swagger docs, RESTful (Registration/loginization/pagination etc.), testing UI and functionality of components, performance optimization, project architectural solutions (UI, BLL, DAL, server), bug fixing and code maintenance.

My other projects

Check knowledge Z

Social network 🗗

Instagram Clone 🗗

Free Math Trainer

Education

 IT-INCUBATOR - frontend developer 2022-2023 Learning and working with React, Redux, TypeScript, Promises, REST API, Git, CSS/SASS, Material UI, TDD, Storybook and other modern frontend technologies

2006-2011 Moscow State University of tourism and service - computer analyst

Learning databases, SQL, Objective Pascal, Delphi, HTML, Math, other fundamental theoretical subjects and other old stuff

Languages

Russian - native English - C1 (in progress)